# **KHANT MAW HEIN**

## Frontend Web Developer



#### **SUMMARY**

React.js(Frontend Developer) with 3 years of experience in designing and developing user interfaces, testing and training employees. Skilled at utilizing a wide variety of tools and programs to provide effective applications. And also developed a lot web site (Business projects) with React.js.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Web Developer Frontend

Visible One-HK

Visible One, based in Singapore, offers expert web design, development, and digital strategy services. Our team specializes in delivering customized, resultsoriented solutions to digitize local businesses, ensuring they keep pace with the latest technology trends.

- Created and maintained 5+ web applications for numerous national and foreign clients
- Ensured that the user interfaces and user experience of the software applications developed by the team met at least 70% of users expectations
- Created and analyzed 100+ unit test cases
- Developed javascripts to automate image's noise-reduction process which helped improve research analysis time by 40%
- Established and lead a team of 10 people; covering every key role in the early stages in our groups

## Front End Web Developer

Light Idea Software Development 苗 2022 - 2023 👂 Larshio, Myanmar Light Idea is software company. developed web and android application and ios application for large and small business company.

- Increased by 35% the reach of users to the platform, over the installation of the web platform in mobile devices
- Delivered 40+ web solutions
- Replaced 1 full-time web developer under part-time employment achieving a productivity gain of over 60% as measured by working hours
- Worked with more than 2 different teams at different points of time and provided end-to-end solutions for clients

# **Full Stack Developer**

Real Code Solution

**#** 2021 - 2022

Mandalav, Myanmar

Real Code Solution is a software house company. Develop a lot of mobile and web application for POS and custom software in Mandalay.

- Developed several application selled 100 app in per years.
- Joined the team as 10 employee as a developer working directly with the biggest customers
- Involved in coding as per the requirement, delivered well ahead of time which saved project cost by 20%
- Reduced database size by nearly 50% and improved its performance by 20%
- Delivery time of good reduced by 50%

# Web Developer

Andfun(Japanese)

**#** 2020 - 2021

Yangon, Myanmar

Andfun is a software house based on japan. It is developed web and android, ios application.

- Developed a lot of customer from japan. Customize some function and features as customer.
- We need to meet with customer directly from japanese.
- Our team met once a day in pre week as to descript for our difficult to negotiate.

### **SKILLS**

PHP _	Scss	React.js	Laravel
MySQL	HTML	.5 CSS	SQL
Javascript Next.js			
Tailwind	MUI	GSAP(3	D animation)
Framer motion AntDesign			
React Bootstrap Vue.js			
Github	Git	Gitlab	

#### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor of Computer Science (Hons)

Yadanarbon University (Mandalay)

苗 2015 - 03/2021 👂 Myanmar, Mandalay

## **STRENGTHS**



## Problem-solver

In my last Real Code Solution, We lost our real database during show example projects, and our CEO call our team and how is that. and then we solved that during that night I, we did not leave the office . We recovered all data all the whole night and till the code was clean and running,



# Result-oriented

I save time and discover more creative ways to do a specific task.

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**



## Winner in Soft-Skill

I have soft-skill to communicate with my team work.and my team always said good leader for them.

CX7 Enhancy